https://teague.com/terms-conditions

>
Terms & Conditions
Acceptance of Terms
This website is owned and operated by TEAGUE, its officers, directors and employees (TEAGUE). TEAGUE offers this site for your personal informational, educational and entertainment use. Please read the following Terms of Use carefully before using this Website - by using the site, you agree to these Terms of Use. If you do NOT agree to these Terms of Use, please do NOT use the TEAGUE website. These Terms of Use apply only to your use of the Website and do not apply to any other Website or any TEAGUE product or service, nor change any other agreement that may exist between you and TEAGUE. TEAGUE reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify or change these Terms of Use at any time without prior notice to you. Your continued use of the website following the posting of any changes to the Terms of Use constitutes your acceptance of such changes.
Accuracy and Completeness of Information
TEAGUE is not responsible if information made available on this site is not accurate, complete or current. The material on this site is provided for general information only, and should not be relied upon or used as the sole basis for making decisions without consulting primary, more accurate, more complete or more timely sources of information. We reserve the right to modify the Contents of this site at any time, but we have no obligation to update any information on the site. You agree that it is your responsibility to monitor changes to the site.
Your Use of the Site
You acknowledge that all Content on this Web Site, including the Web Site's design, graphics, text, formatting, sounds, pictures, images, software, and other materials and information on this Website, and the selection and arrangement thereof (collectively, "Content"), are the property of TEAGUE or its licensors, and are subject to and protected by United States and international copyright and other intellectual property laws and rights. All rights to Content not expressly granted in these Terms of Use are reserved to their respective intellectual property right owners. Except as expressly authorized in these Terms of Use or on the Web Site, you may not copy, reproduce, distribute, republish, download, perform, display, post, transmit, exploit, create derivative works or otherwise use any of the Content in any form or by any means, without the prior written authorization of TEAGUE or the respective intellectual property rights owner. TEAGUE authorizes you to view and download the Content only for personal, non-commercial use, provided that you keep intact all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the original Content. You may not modify or adapt the Content in any way or otherwise use them for any public or commercial purposes.
Materials You Submit
You acknowledge that you are responsible for any information, material or Content you may submit via this website, including but not limited to the legality, reliability, appropriateness, originality and copyright ownership of any such materials or Content. You may not upload to or publish through this site any information, materials or Content that: (i) are false; fraudulent; libelous; defamatory; abusive; obscene; threatening; or otherwise objectionable; confidential; infringing or invasive of privacy or publicity rights; infringing on intellectual property rights; abusive, and/or illegal; (ii) may constitute or incite a criminal offense; violate the rights of any party; or otherwise give rise to liability or violate any law; or (iii) may contain software viruses, worms or any other form of malware; political campaigning; or chain letters; mass mailings; or any form of "spam." You may not use a false email address or other identifying information, impersonate any person or entity or otherwise mislead as to the origin of any information, materials or Content. You may not upload commercial Content onto the site.
If you do submit information, materials or Content, and unless we expressly indicate otherwise, you hereby grant TEAGUE an unrestricted, nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable and fully sublicensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute and display such information, material or Content throughout the world in any media. You further agree that TEAGUE is free to use any ideas, information, concepts, and/or know-how that you or anyone acting on your behalf provide to TEAGUE. You grant TEAGUE the right to use the name you submit in connection with such information, materials or Content, if TEAGUE elects to do so. All personal information provided via this site will be handled in accordance with the site's online Privacy Policy. You represent and warrant that you own or otherwise control all the rights to the information, materials and Content you post; that the information, materials and Content are accurate; that use of the inforamtion, materials and Content you post or provide do not violate any provisions of the Terms of Use and will not cause injury to any individual or entity; and that you will indemnify TEAGUE for all claims resulting from information, materials and Content you post or provide.
Disclaimers
EXCEPT WHERE OTHERWISE EXPRESSLY PROVIDED, THIS SITE AND ALL INFORMATION, MATERIALS AND CONTENT THEREIN ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS. TEAGUE HEREBY EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON INFRINGEMENT. TEAGUE MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT THE SITE, INFORAMTION, MATERIALS AND CONTENT WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, WILL BE AVAILABLE ON AN UNINTERRUPTED OR SECURE BASIS, OR THAT THE QUALITY OF ANY INFORMATION, MATERIALS OR CONTENT OBTAINED BY YOU ON OR THROUGH THE SITE WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS.
IF YOU DOWNLOAD ANY INFORMATION, MATERIAL OR CONTENT FROM THIS SITE, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH INFORMATION, MATERIAL OR CONTENT.
Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL TEAGUE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING OUT OF, IN CONNECTION WITH OR RELATING TO YOUR ACCESS TO, OR USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THIS WEB SITE OR ANY MATERIAL, CONTENT, OR ANY OTHER WEBSITE YOU ACCESS THROUGH A LINK FROM THIS WEB SITE, OR ANY INCORRECT OR INACCURATE INFORMATION ON THIS WEB SITE. THIS IS A COMPREHENSIVE LIMITATION OF LIABILITY THAT APPLIES TO ALL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO PROPOERTY DAMAGE, LOSS OF USE, LOSS OF DATA, LOSS OF BUSINESS, ECONOMIC LOSS OR LOSS OF PROFITS), WHETHER BASED ON BREACH OF CONTRACT, BREACH OF WARRANTY, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE) OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF TEAGUE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBLITY OF SUCH DAMAGE OR LOSS. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, YOU EXPRESSLY WAIVE ALL CLAIMS AGAINST TEAGUE THEIR OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, SUPPLIERS AND PROGRAMMERS THAT MAY ARISE FROM YOUR ACCESS OR USE OF THIS SITE.
YOU SPECIFICALLY ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT NEITHER TEAGUE NOR ITS SUPPLIERS SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DEFAMATORY, OFFENSIVE OR ILLEGAL CONDUCT OF ANY USER OF THE SITE. YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY FOR ANY OF THE ABOVE CLAIMS OR ANY DISPUTE WITH TEAGUE IS TO DISCONTINUE YOUR USE OF THE SITE.
Exclusion of Limitations
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW DISCLAIMERS, EXCLUSIONS OR LIMITATIONS OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES, OR THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO ALL OR A PORTION OF THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN SUCH EVENT, AND NOTWITHSTANDING THAT ANY DISCLAIMER, EXCLUSION, OR LIMITATION OF LIABLITY MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, ALL OTHER PROVISIONS OF THIS TERMS OF USE SHALL APPLY, AND REMAIN IN FULL FORCE AND EFFECT.
Indemnification
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold TEAGUE harmless from and against any and all claims, damages, costs and expenses, including attorney's fees, arising from and related to your use of the site.
Copyright Notice
Unless otherwise noted, the graphic images, buttons and text contained in this site (Graphics) are the exclusive property of TEAGUE. Except as otherwise expressly authorized in the Terms of Use, the Graphics may not be copied, published, distributed, displayed, reproduced, or transmitted, in any form or by any means, including but not limited to electronic, mechanical, photocopying, recording, or otherwise, without prior written permission of TEAGUE.
Trademarks
This website features logos, brand identities and other trademarks and service marks (the "Marks") that are the property of, or are licensed to TEAGUE, its licensors, and/or Content providers. All Marks are the property of their respective owners. Nothing contained on this site should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use any Mark displayed on this site without written permission of TEAGUE or any third party that may own a Mark displayed on the site. TEAGUE reserves all rights not expressly granted in and to the site and its Content. This site and all of its Content, including but not limited to text, design, graphics, interfaces and code, and the selection and arrangement thereof, is protected as a compilation under the copyright laws of the United States and other countries.
Links to Third Party Sites
As a convenience to visitors and users, this website may link to other sites owned and operated by third parties and not owned or maintained by TEAGUE. However, even if such third parties are affiliated with TEAGUE, TEAGUE has no control over these linked sites, all of which have separate privacy and data collection practices and legal policies independent of TEAGUE. TEAGUE is not and shall not be responsible for the information, materials or Content of any linked sites and does not make any representations regarding the Content or accuracy of information, materials or Content on such sites. Accessing and using such third party sites is entirely at your own risk.
Privacy Policy
TEAGUE respects your Privacy, and has developed a policy to address privacy concerns. For more information, please see TEAGUE's Privacy Policy. Any personal information collected on this site will be treated in accordance with TEAGUE's Privacy Policy.
Minors' Use of the Site.
Minors (individuals under 13 years of age) are not eligible or authorized to view or use the site, and we ask that they do not submit any information, Content or materials to us.
Cautionary Language Regarding Forward-Looking Statements
This website may contain statements, estimates or projections that constitute "forward-looking statements" as defined under U.S. federal securities laws. Any such forward-looking statements are inherently speculative and are based on currently available information, operating plans and projections about future events and trends. As such, they are subject to numerous risks and uncertainties. Actual results and performance may be significantly different from TEAGUE's historical experience and our present expectations or projections. TEAGUE undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements.
Jurisdiction
These Terms of Use are governed and interpreted under the laws of the State of Washington, United States of America, without regard to its choice of law provisions. By using this site you consent to the jurisdiction of the federal and state courts located in Washington for any action or claim arising from or relating to these Terms of Use. If any portion of these Terms of Use is deemed unlawful, void, or unenforceable, then that portion shall be deemed to be severable and shall be construed in accordance with applicable law. Such portion will not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions or terms. TEAGUE's failure to act with respect to a breach of these Terms of Use by you or others does not constitute a waiver of the Terms of Use and shall not limit TEAGUE's rights with respect to such breach or any subsequent breaches.
Export Restrictions/Legal Compliance
You may not access, download, use or export the site, or the materials and Content provided on or through the site, in violation of U.S. export laws or regulations, or in violation of any other applicable laws or regulations. You agree to comply with all export laws and restrictions and regulations of any United States or foreign agency or authority, and not to directly or indirectly provide or otherwise make available the services and products of TEAGUE in violation of any such restrictions, laws or regulations, or without all necessary approvals, including, without limitation, for the development, design, manufacture or production of nuclear, chemical or biological weapons of mass destruction and of missile technology. As applicable, you shall obtain and bear all expenses relating to any necessary licenses and/or exemptions with respect to your own use of the services of TEAGUE outside the U.S. Neither the services of TEAGUE nor the underlying information or technology may be downloaded or otherwise provided or made available, either directly or indirectly, into: (a) all countries subject to U.S. trade sanctions, to individuals or entities controlled by such countries, or to nationals or residents of such countries other than nationals who are lawful permanent residents of countries not subject to such sanctions; or (b) to anyone on the U.S. Treasury Department's list of Specially Designated Nationals and Blocked Persons or the U.S. Commerce Department's Table of Denial Orders. By agreeing to these Terms of Use, you agree to the foregoing and represent and warrant that you are not located in, under the control of, or a national or resident of any such country or on any such list.
You agree not to use the Web Site for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these terms and conditions. You further agree that you are responsible for your use of and communications on the Web Site. You agree not to post on or transmit through this Web Site any unlawful, infringing, threatening, harassing, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, profane, indecent, offensive, hateful or otherwise objectionable material of any kind, including any material that encourages criminal conduct or conduct that would give rise to civil liability, violates the privacy rights of others, infringes others' intellectual property rights or otherwise violates any applicable local, state, national or international law. You agree not to use this Web Site in any manner that interferes with its normal operation or with any other user's use and enjoyment of the Site. You agree to use reasonable efforts to scan and remove any viruses or other contaminating or destructive features before submitting any material.
TEAGUE reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to suspend or terminate your access to this Web Site and prohibit any and all current and future use of this Web Site (or any portion thereof) by you, if you fail to comply with any term or provision of these Terms of Use or your use is harmful to the interests of another user of this Web Site.
Contact Information
If you have any questions regarding these Terms of Use, please contact TEAGUE at info@teague.com. If you have any other questions, contact information is available at www.teague.com.
Newsletter
Teague © 2020
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
We're using cookies to deliver you the best user experience. Learn More
New Business
Press
General
No maker of things today works alone.
Walter Dorwin Teague
